<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maira Martins K</title>
    <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maira Martins K</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:46:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mairamartins.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Summit 2018</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/web-summit-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:46:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/web-summit-2018/</guid>
      <description>I came home a few days ago from my first tech conference, Web Summit 2018, and I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my thoughts about it from the point of view of a newcomer to the industry.
It is crazy!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been to large photography conferences before, but Web Summit is massive in a whole different scale. I&amp;rsquo;m talking almost 70.000 attendees, 3 full-days of talks and workshops, a ton of startups, and people of the caliber of Tony Blair and Tim Berners-Lee giving presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 06:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is my second attempt at a programming blog. The first time was about a year ago, right when I first started to learn web development and unfortunately I was overcome with impostor syndrome and ended up deleting all the posts. I kinda regret that I didn&amp;rsquo;t keep at it. It would have been so nice to go back and read about my many discoveries and challenges.
(You hear that, reader from the future?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Maira, a Brazilian/Swedish web developer living in Barcelona. Lover of CSS, dogs, sushi and React.js (in no order of preference).
 My passion for web development started at age 15 (back in the year 2000, yo!), when I bought a &amp;ldquo;How to Build a Website - For Dummies&amp;rdquo; book. From that moment on, my life got filled with iframes, inline styles and a unique design that can only be described as a mix of brutalism and minimalism at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>