<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Maira Martins K</title>
    <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Maira Martins K</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 11:19:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mairamartins.com/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CS50, an intro to Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/cs50-week0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 11:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/cs50-week0/</guid>
      <description>I started CS50 a couple weeks ago, with a goal of getting it done during this second round of #100DaysOfCode, but with the Web Summit and job-hunting and trying to complete two freeCodeCamp certifications, I kind of let CS50 slide.
What is CS50 CS50 is Harvard&amp;rsquo;s University intro to Computer Science, that I am taking for free as a self-paced course through EdX.
As a front end web developer I don&amp;rsquo;t really need to know computer science concepts to do my job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Style Highlighted Text with CSS</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/css-selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 10:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/css-selection/</guid>
      <description>Today I was trying to decide what content to write about, when I accidently highlighted some text on my own blog.
Normally, the background color of the highlighted portion shows up in blue, in the same shade as the browser&amp;rsquo;s default focus color. While this is not a bad thing at all, I would prefer it to match my color palette (black, yellow, white).
Never having styled a highlight before, I set out to discover how to do it and, 60 seconds later, it was done!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Podcasts for Beginner Developers</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/podcasts-beginner-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:49:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/podcasts-beginner-developer/</guid>
      <description>It took me a long time to enjoy the idea of listening to programming podcasts. Since for the past year I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying so many hours (30h to 40h/week), I really wanted to use my podcast time to disconnect.
As a beginner, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to feel overwhelmed by everything you don&amp;rsquo;t know. I still prefer to listen to podcasts about everything else, but when I want to learn about web development, those are my go-to shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Podcasts About Everything</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/best-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 16:50:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/best-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Since I discovered the world of podcasts in early 2015, my consumption of music has declined steadily.
Podcasts became my go-to source of general knowledge and entertainment and are a big part of my daily routine. I can’t listen to them if I’m at the computer though. I forget I’m listening to them and seem to focus only on the screen in front of me. Rewinding does nothing, as within 3 seconds I stop listening again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Summit 2018</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/web-summit-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:46:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/web-summit-2018/</guid>
      <description>I came home a few days ago from my first tech conference, Web Summit 2018, and I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my thoughts about it from the point of view of a newcomer to the industry.
It is crazy!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been to large photography conferences before, but Web Summit is massive in a whole different scale. I&amp;rsquo;m talking almost 70.000 attendees, 3 full-days of talks and workshops, a ton of startups, and people of the caliber of Tony Blair and Tim Berners-Lee giving presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 06:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is my second attempt at a programming blog. The first time was about a year ago, right when I first started to learn web development and unfortunately I was overcome with impostor syndrome and ended up deleting all the posts. I kinda regret that I didn&amp;rsquo;t keep at it. It would have been so nice to go back and read about my many discoveries and challenges.
(You hear that, reader from the future?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>