<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Maira Martins K</title>
    <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/tags/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Maira Martins K</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:49:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mairamartins.com/blog/tags/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Podcasts for Beginner Developers</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/podcasts-beginner-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:49:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/podcasts-beginner-developer/</guid>
      <description>It took me a long time to enjoy the idea of listening to programming podcasts. Since for the past year I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying so many hours (30h to 40h/week), I really wanted to use my podcast time to disconnect.
As a beginner, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to feel overwhelmed by everything you don&amp;rsquo;t know. I still prefer to listen to podcasts about everything else, but when I want to learn about web development, those are my go-to shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Podcasts About Everything</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/best-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 16:50:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/best-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Since I discovered the world of podcasts in early 2015, my consumption of music has declined steadily.
Podcasts became my go-to source of general knowledge and entertainment and are a big part of my daily routine. I can’t listen to them if I’m at the computer though. I forget I’m listening to them and seem to focus only on the screen in front of me. Rewinding does nothing, as within 3 seconds I stop listening again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Summit 2018</title>
      <link>https://mairamartins.com/blog/web-summit-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:46:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mairamartins.com/blog/web-summit-2018/</guid>
      <description>I came home a few days ago from my first tech conference, Web Summit 2018, and I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my thoughts about it from the point of view of a newcomer to the industry.
It is crazy!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been to large photography conferences before, but Web Summit is massive in a whole different scale. I&amp;rsquo;m talking almost 70.000 attendees, 3 full-days of talks and workshops, a ton of startups, and people of the caliber of Tony Blair and Tim Berners-Lee giving presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>